<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2013 Jason Barkes

     Android QB Rating App
     Jason Barkes - http://jbarkes.blogspot.com

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, this software is
     provided on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND,
     either express or implied.
-->

<resources>
    <string name="app_eula_accept">OK</string>
    <string name="app_eula_title">End User License Agreement (EULA)</string>
    <string name="app_eula_text">
        This End-User License Agreement (“EULA”) is a legal agreement between you (either an individual or a single entity), the end-user,
        and the author of the QB Calculator Software ("Owner"). This EULA permits you to use a single copy, or multiples copies of the software product
        identified above, which includes computer software and may include associated media, printed materials, and on-line or electronic documentation.
        By installing, copying, or otherwise using the QB Calculator Software, you agree to be bounded by the terms of this EULA. If you do not agree
        to the terms of this EULA, do not install or use the QB Calculator Software.
        Do not use the Software until you have carefully read the following Agreement.

        \n\n1. GRANT OF LICENSE

        \n\nSubject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, you are granted a limited, non-exclusive, license to download, install, and use
        the QB Calculator Software. The QB Calculator software is licensed, not sold.

        \n\n2. RESTRICTIONS

        \n\nYou may not decompile, disassemble or otherwise reverse engineer the QB Calculator software, or engage in any other activities
        to obtain underlying information that is not visible to the user in connection with normal use of the QB Calculator software. You
        agree not to modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute, or create derivative works based upon this software. You agree not to
        publicize or distribute any registration code algorithms, information, or registration codes used by this software without permission
        from the Owner. You may not use the QB Calculator Software to engage in or allow others to engage in any illegal activity where
        the QB Calculator Software is accessed and used. You may not use the QB Calculator Software to engage in any activity that will
        violate the rights of third parties, including, without limitation, through the use, public display, public performance, reproduction,
        distribution, or modification of communications or materials that infringe copyrights, trademarks, publicity rights, privacy rights,
        other proprietary rights, or rights against defamation of third parties.

        \n\n3. OWNERSHIP

        \n\nThis license provides you with limited rights to use the QB Calculator Software. The Owner retains all ownership, right, title
        and interest in, to and of the QB Calculator Software and all copies of it. All rights not specifically granted in this license,
        including domestic and international copyrights, are reserved by Jason Barkes.

        \n\n4. COPYRIGHT

        \n\nThis software is protected by copyright laws and international copyright treaties, as well as other intellectual property laws and treaties.

        \n\n5. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES

        \n\nTHE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS,” WITH NO WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER. THE OWNER EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS TO THE
        FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ALL EXPRESS, IMPLIED, AND STATUTORY WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES
        OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS AND ANY WARRANTIES
        REGARDING THE SECURITY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND PERFORMANCE OF THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE. THE OWNER DOES NOT WARRANT
        THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, THAT THE OPERATION OF THE QB CALCULATOR
        SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS IN THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE WILL BE CORRECTED. THE OWNER
        DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE IN
        TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OR OTHERWISE. THE OWNER DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT USERS WILL
        BE ABLE TO ACCESS OR USE THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE AT TIMES OR LOCATIONS OF THEIR CHOOSING, OR THAT THE OWNER WILL HAVE
        ADEQUATE CAPACITY FOR ANY USER’S REQUIREMENTS. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN STATEMENT, INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY THE OWNER, OR
        RESPECTIVE EMPLOYEES, DISTRIBUTORS, DEALERS, OR AGENTS SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTIES.

        \n\nYOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR DOWNLOAD AND/OR USE OF THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE IS AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND
        THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGES TO YOUR DEVICE OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OR USE OF THE
        QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE.

        \n\nSOME STATES OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT
        APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM STATE TO STATE AND JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.

        \n\n6. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

        \n\nUNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL THE OWNER, OR SUPPLIERS, RESELLERS, PARTNERS OR RESPECTIVE AFFILIATES BE LIABLE
        FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING FROM OR RELATED TO THE QB
        CALCULATOR SOFTWARE, WHETHER SUCH CLAIM IS BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE, (EVEN
        IF ANY SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES). WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, THE TOTAL AGGREGATE
        LIABILITY OF THE OWNER, AND HIS SUPPLIERS, RESELLERS, PARTNERS AND RESPECTIVE AFFILIATES ARISING FROM OR RELATED
        TO THIS AGREEMENT SHALL NOT EXCEED THE AMOUNT, IF ANY, PAID BY YOU TO THE OWNER FOR THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE. IF THE
        QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED WITHOUT CHARGE, THEN THE OWNER AND SUPPLIERS SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY TO YOU WHATSOEVER.

        \n\nTHE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARISE FROM USE OR MISUSE OF AND RELIANCE ON THE QB
        CALCULATOR SOFTWARE, FROM INABILITY TO USE THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE, TO USE, OR FROM THE INTERRUPTION, SUSPENSION, OR
        TERMINATION OF THE QB CALCULATOR SOFTWARE (INCLUDING SUCH DAMAGES INCURRED BY THIRD PARTIES). SUCH LIMITATION SHALL APPLY
        NOTWITHSTANDING A FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY LIMITED REMEDY AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. SOME STATES
        OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR DIRECT DAMAGES,
        SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

        \n\n7. MISCELLANEOUS

        \n\nThe Owner reserves the right to modify or amend this Agreement at any time and for any reason or for no reason at all,
        at his sole discretion, without notice.

        \n\nIf any provision in this Agreement should be held illegal or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, such
        provision shall be modified to the extent necessary to render it enforceable without losing its intent, or severed from
        this Agreement if no such modification is possible, and other provisions of this Agreement shall remain in full force and
        effect. A waiver by either party of any term or condition of this Agreement or any breach thereof, in any one instance,
        shall not waive such term or condition or any subsequent breach thereof.

    </string>
</resources>